# **AGARACH TAMMAGUL**

Civil Engineer / Planner & Designer Khonkaen University # 45



### **PROFILE**

I took the role of on-site Construction Project Manager of the projects assigned me. I worked and communicated with cusand alients directly

I had excellent communication skill which helped me to communicate and my points clearly and precisely to members of various levels in the organization namely engineers. contactors and clients

## PRO SKILL

Microsoft Office			
POOR	FAIR	GOOD	EXCELLENT
Autocad & Design			
POOR	FAIR	GOOD	EXCELLENT
3D Builder & Rendering Graphic			
POOR	FAIR	GOOD	EXCELLENT
English Comunication (Write / Read / Speech)			
POOR	FAIR	GOOD	EXCELLENT











098-540-8840



Egarach T@hotmail.com



**Maptaphut Rayong Thailand** 

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 13 August 1986

Marital Status : Married

Nationality: Thai

Religion: Buddhism

## **EDUCATION**

2006 Rajamangala University of Technology ISAN Khonkaen Campus

Diploma Builder

2012 Khonkaen University

Bachelor Degree of Civil Engineering

## WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - Present

## AS First Company Limited (Rayong Thailand)

**Last Position : Construction Manager / Estimator** Project: - SPRC Maintanance Plant Project & ETC.

- (Approximate 150 million Baht) Provided how to work correctly of construction with engineering knowledge
- Marketing & Estimator for new site

#### 2017 - 2018 Siam Titan Company Limited (Rayong Thailand)

Last Position: Project Manager

Project: - PTT-ME New Cable Route Line Project ( 166 Million Baht)

- GLOW Improve Transformer & New Foundation ( 46 Million Baht)
- BST New Unit Foundation (Shut Down Work) ( 18 Million Baht)
- Solve immediate problems to possible safe cost & time
- Delayed Management for work catch up possible follow master planning
- Marketing & Estimator for new site

#### 2015 - 2017 Viking Construction Company Limited (Rayong Thailand)

**Last Position: Project Manager** 

Project: - IRPC Rayong Clean Power Plant (Rayong) (185 Million)

- Solve immediate problems to possible safe cost & time
- Delayed Management for work catch up possible follow master planning
- **Ensure period of construction for deliver to TTCL (Main Contract)**
- Coordinated with third party and TTCL (Main Contract) for handover work Estimate prepared budgetary for bidding (Present Owner)
- Marketing & Estimator for new site

#### 2012 - 2015 Nawarat Patanakarn Pulic Company Limited (Rayong Thailand)

**Last Position: Project Engineer** 

Project: - CPF Food Manufacturing factory (Nongjok) (115 Milion Baht)

- Chana Power Plant II (Songkla) (1,865 Million Baht)
- Veranda Beach Pattava Hotel (Pattava) (466 Miliom Baht)
- Provided how to work correctly of construction with engineering knowledge
- Solve immediate problems to possible safe cost & time
- QA/QC for quality control document
- **Engineering Design for equality (Change Work)**
- Prepared work method statement for ensure to each work activity
- Delayed Management for work catch up possible follow master planning

### 2006 - 2012 Khonkaen Warasiri Housing Estate (Khonkaen Thailand)

**Last Position : Civil Supervisor** 

Project: - Housing Estate Branded " WARASIRI " (300 Million Baht)

- Control quality of construction such as how to work correctly
- Performed request for material & storage
- Ensure period of construction for deliver to customers